[
  { 
    "id": 1.1,
    "name": "Hiragana",
    "card": [
    {
      "id":1,
      "question": "あ",
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "id":2,
      "question": "い",
      "answer": "i"
    },
    {
    "id":3,
      "question": "う",
      "answer": "u"
    },
    {
    "id":4,
      "question": "え",
      "answer": "e"
    },
    {
    "id":5,
      "question": "お",
      "answer": "o"
    },
    {
    "id":6,
      "question": "か",
      "answer": "ka"
    },
    {
    "id":7,
      "question": "き",
      "answer": "ki"
    },
    {
    "id":8,
      "question": "く",
      "answer": "ku"
    },
    {
    "id":9,
      "question": "け",
      "answer": "ke"
    },
    {
    "id":10,
      "question": "こ",
      "answer": "ko"
    },
    {
    "id":11,
      "question": "さ",
      "answer": "sa"
    },
    {
    "id":12,
      "question": "し",
      "answer": "shi"
    },
    {
    "id":13,
      "question": "す",
      "answer": "su"
    },
    {
    "id":14,
      "question": "せ",
      "answer": "se"
    },
    {
    "id":15,
      "question": "そ",
      "answer": "so"
    },
    {
    "id":16,
      "question": "た",
      "answer": "ta"
    },
    {
    "id":17,
      "question": "ち",
      "answer": "chi"
    },
    {
    "id":18,
      "question": "つ",
      "answer": "tsu"
    },
    {
    "id":19,
      "question": "て",
      "answer": "te"
    },
    {
    "id":20,
      "question": "と",
      "answer": "to"
    },
    {
    "id":21,
      "question": "な",
      "answer": "na"
    },
    {
    "id":22,
      "question": "に",
      "answer": "ni"
    },
    {
    "id":23,
      "question": "ぬ",
      "answer": "nu"
    },
    {
    "id":24,
      "question": "ね",
      "answer": "ne"
    },
    {
    "id":25,
      "question": "の",
      "answer": "no"
    },
    {
    "id":26,
      "question": "は",
      "answer": "ha"
    },
    {
    "id":27,
      "question": "ひ",
      "answer": "hi"
    },
    {
    "id":28,
      "question": "ふ",
      "answer": "fu"
    },
    {
    "id":29,
      "question": "へ",
      "answer": "he"
    },
    {
    "id":30,
      "question": "ほ",
      "answer": "ho"
    },
    {
    "id":31,
      "question": "ま",
      "answer": "ma"
    },
    {
    "id":32,
      "question": "み",
      "answer": "mi"
    },
    {
    "id":33,
      "question": "む",
      "answer": "mu"
    },
    {
    "id":34,
      "question": "め",
      "answer": "me"
    },
    {
    "id":35,
      "question": "も",
      "answer": "mo"
    },
    {
    "id":36,
      "question": "か",
      "answer": "ka"
    },
    {
    "id":37,
      "question": "や",
      "answer": "ya"
    },
    {
    "id":38,
      "question": "ゆ",
      "answer": "yu"
    },
    {
    "id":39,
      "question": "よ",
      "answer": "yo"
    },
    {
    "id":40,
      "question": "ら",
      "answer": "ra"
    },
    {
    "id":41,
      "question": "り",
      "answer": "ri"
    },
    {
    "id":42,
      "question": "る",
      "answer": "ru"
    },
    {
    "id":43,
      "question": "れ",
      "answer": "re"
    },
    {
    "id":44,
      "question": "ろ",
      "answer": "ro"
    },
    {
    "id":45,
      "question": "わ",
      "answer": "wa"
    },
    {
    "id":46,
      "question": "を",
      "answer": "wo"
    },
    {
    "id":47,
      "question": "ん",
      "answer": "nn"
    }
    ]
  },
  { 
    "id": 1.2,
    "name": "Food",
    "card": [
    {
      "id":1,
      "question": "おいしい",
      "answer": "delicious"
    },
    {
      "id":2,
      "question": "さかな",
      "answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "id":3,
      "question": "とんかつ",
      "answer": "pork cutlet"
    },
    {
      "id":4,
      "question": "メニュー",
      "answer": "menu"
    },
    {
      "id":5,
      "question": "やさい",
      "answer": "vegetable"
    },
    {
      "id":6,
      "question":"にく",
      "answer":"meat"
    }
    ]
  },
  { 
    "id": 1.3,
    "name": "Places",
    "card": [
    {
      "id":1,
      "question": "きっさてん",
      "answer": "cafe",
      "english": "kissaten"
    },
    {
      "id":2,
      "question": "ぎんこう",
      "answer": "bank",
      "english": "ginkou"
    },
    {
      "id":3,
      "question": "としょかん",
      "answer": "library",
      "english": "toshokan"
    },
    {
      "id":4,
      "question": "ゆうびんきょく",
      "answer": "post office",
      "english": "yuubinkyoku"
    }]
  },
  { 
    "id": 1.4,
    "name": "subject4",
    "card": [
    {
      "id":1,
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "answer"
    },
    {
      "id":2,
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "answer"
    },
    {
      "id":3,
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "answer"
    }]
  },
  { 
    "id": 1.5,
    "name": "subject5",
    "card": [
    {
      "id":1,
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "answer"
    },
    {
      "id":2,
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "answer"
    },
    {
      "id":3,
      "question": "question?",
      "answer": "answer"
    }]
  }
]